

ANAND K

3D VISUALIZER & 2D DRAFTSMAN

CONTACT ME

IND: 91 8156865775 UAE: 97 0501410320

anand3hd@gmail.com

www.ananddesigner.in

😯 Kattangal, Calicut, Kerala

FOLLOW ME

f facebook/Anand Gopalan

inkedin/anand k

instagram/anand

behance/anand K

LANGUAGE

MALALAYALAM

ENGLISH

TAMIL

HINDI

HOBBIES

Traveling Swimming

Chess Music



ABOUT ME

My Name Is Anand This is my personal resume where I like to experiment with images and new designs. I am Senior 3D Visualizer with passion for 3D Modeling. I have been working with 3D for twelve years. Creating Interior, Exterior and 2D etc. I have worked with graphic design to be incorporated in my 3d design views. Realization of projects is an added satisfaction as you can see your projects from conceptual to reality.



EDUCATION

> AURIGA MULTIMEDIA JUNE 2006 - DEC 2007

Digital art and audio visual engineering, Thalassery, Kerala

> HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL JUNE 2002 - DEC 2004

Plus two higher secondary board, Iritty, Kerala

> HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL JUNE 2001 - DEC 2002

SSLC, State education board, Iritty, Kerala



WORK EXPERIENCE

> 3D VISUALIZER AND 2D DRAFTSMAN FEB 2022 - PRESENT

SKYLIGHT, Mukkam

> 3D VISUALIZER AND 2D DRAFTSMAN MAR 2020 - FEB 2022

 $USI\ DESIGN, Meen chanda, Calicut.$

> 3D VISUALIZER AND 2D DRAFTSMAN DEC 2018 - JAN 2020

DASC EXHIBITION & INTERIORS, Sharjah, UAE.

> 3D VISUALIZER AND 2D DRAFTSMAN AUG 2015 - DEC 2018

MUHZIN ASSOCIATES, Kunnamangalam, Calicut.

> 3D VISUALIZER AND 2D DRAFTSMAN JUN 2014 - MAY 2015

QUAAF DESIGN at suadi arabia

> 3D VISUALIZER AND 2D DRAFTSMAN SEPT 2010 - FEB 2014

SALEEM GROUP, Mankavu, Calicut



SKILLS

3DS MAX,VRAY ● ● ● ●	AUTOCAD	• • • • •
PHOTOSHOP • • • •	LUMION	• • • • •
ILLUSTRATOR • • • •	WORD	• • • • •
DREAMWEAVER • • • •	FLASH	• • • • •